[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Простуда' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かぜ"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відрядження' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅっちょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відрядженняїхати у відрядження' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅっちょうします"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Будь здоров, бережи себе' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おだいじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Що трапилось?' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "どうしましたか"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Літати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Переносити, переставляти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はこびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Повертати (на попереднє місце)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もどします"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зірка' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ほし"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Світ, блиск, промінь' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひかり"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Небо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そら"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Звук' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おと"
    }
]